"lt seems today that all you see
"is violence in movies and sex on TV
"but where are those good,
old-fashioned values
"on which we used to rely?
"Lucky there's a family guy
"Lucky there's a man who'll
positively tell you
"all the things that make us
"laugh 'n' cry
"He's a family guy"
l say, Rupert, these crumpets
you've prepared look positively divine!
Excellent texture, provocative support.
Try another, you say?
Aren't l the wicked one?
Stewie, l've told you before, don't eat dirt.
lt's disgusting.
And l suppose the bilious curds
you force-fed me from your teat...
...were perfectly fine then?
- Glen, would you mind holding Stewie?
- Said and done.
Hey there, spud with the mud.
Good Lord! Do you bathe in Aqua Velva?
Hi. You've got our votes.
Thank you, Cleveland.
Someone has to run against
that awful Betsy Lebeau.
She actually opposes background checks
for new teachers!
God knows who she might hire.
So the square of a hypotenuse,
which we will label C...
...making the sides opposite both of the
acute angles A and B...
...always equals the sum
of the squares of the other sides.
Any questions?
lt's just something l have to do.
Even if winning means spending time
out of the house and away from my family.
Out of the house? Why, l'd be free
from your oppressive gynocracy!
You should be out giving speeches,
shaking hands, kissing babies!
Not this baby!
Lois, you seen my pants?
Boy, l'll be glad when that studio audience
moves out of the neighborhood.
Lois, what's with the sign?
Peter, we discussed this.
l'm running for School Board.
You never listen to me.
Yeah, l remember.
Hey, Cleveland. Hey, Quagmire.
Lois, what's with the sign?
You guys? Chris' principal just called.
Chris is in trouble.
That's it! l'm calling the cops!
Mr. Griffin, l'm afraid
l have bad news.
l caught your son peeking
into the girls' locker room.
Oh, Chris!
So what's the big deal?
lt's normal for a boy his age to be curious.
l remember when l first noticed
girls starting to develop.
WeIcome to
eighth grade orientation, everyone,
Locker assignments wiII be handed out
in the Iibrary after Iunch period,
If you have any questions
about your Iocker assignments...
...or your cIass scheduIe, pIease come...,
We'll continue this discussion
tonight, young man.
A woman is not an object.
Your mother is right, son.
Listen to what it says.
- Peter!
- l didn't say that.
Lee Majors did.
What? Women are things.
Oh, my God! lt's Mr. Fargas!
He was my favorite teacher!
Take out your scalpels, kids.
We're going to dissect a clown!
No wonder this clown died.
His lungs are filled with candy!
Why don't you go say hello?
l'm gonna drop off some campaign flyers
in the teachers' lounge.
Hey, Mr. Fargas!
lt's me, Peter Griffin!
Griffin. Sorry, not on the list.
Don't you remember me?
l was your favorite student.
You taught me everything. Math, science.
You even taught me how
to dance just in time for the prom.
Peter, you start like this.
Like this?
Yeah. Now add a little turn
and do a buck and wing.
Come on, Mr. Fargas,
do the whole darn thing.
Jeez, Mr. Fargas, what happened to you?
Somebody give you a fun-ectomy?
No, they gave me these
by order of the School Board.
They said it evens me out.
Sorry to fly off the handle.
Here, let me see that.
That's what l think about you taking
chill pills from the Man.
Look, the old Farg made learning fun.
He's what these kids need.
Now get back in that classroom
and teach your "Fargin"' ass off.
Don't come in! Just a minute!
Chris, your mother wants me and you
to have a talk.
No!
l was going for a new record.
Now, son, as men, it's only natural for us
to look at naked girls.
Every man does it, even Mr. Rogers.
Hello, neighbor.
But peeping can be dangerous,
so l brought you this.
- Wow! Miss December!
- Yep, the old skin bin.
Now you can look at naked girls
all you want and it's perfectly legal!
Wow, check out the rack on.... Mom?
Give me that!
Just a little present your mom gave me
for our anniversary.
All right, Dad!
Hey, Dad. Thanks.
Mom, if you get elected
can you fix it so l win Homecoming Queen?
Honey, of course l can.
But winning without honor
isn't really winning at all.
- lsn't that right, Milli?
- No, it's just as good.
"Baby"
What's the use? You're right.
Cease this prattling!
This campaign literature must be posted
today to get you into office...
...and out of my life,
you festering strumpet!
Hey, you guys.
Lois, you running for School Board?
Look, Chris' school is on TV.
The egg drop, an annuaI tradition
for junior-high-schooI science students,
Today at Buddy Cianci Junior High,
an egg drop conducted by teacher...
...RandaII Fargas seems to have gone
horribIy wrong,
We now go Iive to Action News 5
Asian reporter, Trisha Takanawa,
Tom, the eggs being dropped behind me
are not chicken eggs...
...but those of the endangered
CaIifornia condor,
Welcome back, Fargas.
Oh, my God. He's gonna wipe
that species off the face of the earth!
No, Lois. The janitor'll do that.
I'm getting word
that the Quahog SchooI Board...
...has just dismissed RandaII Fargas,
ending his 32-year teaching career,
- What? They can't do that!
- Peter, the man is obviously unbalanced.
In other news, Betsy Lebeau,
SchooI Board President candidate...
...announced today she's puIIing out
of the race,
Lebeau's withdrawaI Ieaves housewife,
Lois Griffin, running unopposed,
My goodness! l win by default!
Great. You can get Mr. Fargas his job back.
l'm sorry! But l do have a mind of my own!
And l happen to agree
with the School Board's decision.
l know you're a feminist
and l think that's adorable...
...but this is grown-up time
and l'm the man.
l'm not giving that lunatic his job back
and that's final.
Lois, l can't let you deprive our children
of a fine teacher like Mr. Fargas.
l'm gonna stop you the only way l can...
...by killing you...
...in the race for School Board President!
Peter, are you sure running against Lois
is such a good idea?
You know how competitive you get.
l can be just as non-competitive
as anybody.
Matter of fact,
l'm the most non-competitive. So l win.
Come on, you can't even handle
losing at checkers.
King me.
Look over there!
What?
Peter, since when do you care
about the School Board?
Lois, Mr. Fargas is getting a bum rap...
...and if running against you
is the only way to get him back...
...then l am gonna run
like the Six Million Dollar Man.
We can rebuild him.
We have the technology,
but l don't want to spend a lot of money.
Fine, if you feel that strongly,
then by all means run.
But l'm warning you, l'm not gonna
pull any punches on the issues.
l'm Lois.
Look at me with my big ideas
and my pointy nose,
This'll be even easier
than running unopposed.
ls that so?
Not only am l gonna win this election...
...l am gonna eat your nose.
See you on the campaign trail.
Oh, my. Look where my hand is.
I say, Iook where my hand is!
It's in a very naughty pIace,
Does that not disgust you?
You're talking to a guy
who uses his tongue for toilet paper.
Now look here, you loathsome cur!
The matron of prattle
has left me in your ward.
You should be striving to thwart
my noisome misdeeds.
Look at me.
l'm writing profanity on the wall!
Water-soluble.
Don't just sit there! l have misbehaved!
l've been a bawdy little monkey!
lf that vile woman were here,
she'd prove a worthy adversary.
What's the matter?
Miss your mommy?
Yes, that's it. That's quite good.
Yes, l miss my mommy.
- l also miss colic and rectal thermometry.
- Whatever you say, Mama's boy.
Blast!
Hey, Chris! Hector found two rocks outside
that look like boobs! You in?
Who needs rocks when you got these?
- Check it out!
- Wow!
Vote for Peter Griffin!
Look at all of Lois' signs!
Talk about seeing red.
Peter, l'm concerned that your candidacy
may have become a lost cause.
The debate is tonight and you don't seem
to have any supporters.
Don't sweat it, the Griffin men
have always been winners...
...dating back to my diminutive
great-grandfather, Juarez Griffin.
Fellas, the debate's in the bag, all right?
lf there's one thing l can do,
it's play to a crowd.
Lois Griffin, daughter of shipping
industriaIist, Carter Pewterschmidt...
...and passive-aggressivist,
Barbara Pewterschmidt,
Tonight she takes on
her greatest chaIIenge, Peter Griffin...
...Quahog's native son, seIf-described
Huguenot, don't know what that means...
...and community activist,
Go, Dad.
He can't hear you.
Go, Dad!
So fasten your seat beIts,
We're just minutes away...
...from Lois versus Peter,
Griffin versus Griffin...
...on Monday Night Debate, y'aII!
"Of suns and worlds l nothing had
to say l see mankind's self-torturing pains"
No! You're doing it wrong!
When you read Faust...
...you're supposed to do Mephistopheles
in a scary voice like this!
ls that the way Mommy reads it?
l do not miss that ogress.
She can burn in hell for all l care!
Sure she can.
Damn!
"l've grown accustomed to her face
"She almost makes the day begin
"l've grown accustomed to the tune
that she whistles night and noon
"Her smiles, her frowns,
her ups, her downs
"are second nature to me now
"Like breathing out and breathing in
"l'm very grateful she's a woman
"and so easy to forget,
rather like a habit one can always break
"And yet,
l've grown accustomed to her looks
"Accustomed to her voice
"Accustomed to her
"face"
Damn you all!
Mr, Griffin,
your opening statement, pIease,
Okay, I'm Peter Griffin, Vote for me,
- Is that it?
- No, this is it,
This is Iife, the one you get,
so go and have a baII...
...because the worId don't move
to the beat of just one drum,
What might be right for you,
may not be right for some,
You take the good, you take the bad...
...you take them both, and there you have
my opening statement,
Sit, Ubu, sit, Good dog,
Okay, Mrs, Griffin?
As a piano teacher, I know how
difficuIt the education process can be,
That's why, if I'm eIected,
I promise to fight for competent teachers...
...a better-funded music department
and updated textbooks...
...that don't refer to the
CiviI Rights Movement as "troubIe ahead, "
Mr, Griffin, your response?
Maybe something about education?
I have aIways cared deepIy
about young peopIe,
As a rich coIIege-bound student, I once
joined some underpriviIeged youths...
...in saving a community center
from being converted into a shopping maII,
Peter, that wasn't you,
That was AdoIpho Shabba-Doo
Electric Boogaloo,
You watched it Iast night,
So you're caIIing me a Iiar?
I'm gonna take the highroad
and stick to the issues,
The chiIdren of Quahog
are our greatest treasure,
They deserve a schooI board president who
doesn't Ieave their feminine ointments...
...in the fridge next to the mustard!
That was the worst hot dog I ever ate!
Yeah, she fIosses in bed,
she snores Iike a wiIdebeest--
Thank you, Mr, Griffin,
We now move on--
Wait a second, bIow dryer,
I'm not done yet,
She freed WiIIie Horton, naiIed Donna Rice--
- Peter, that's enough!
- Eats babies,
Peter, Peter.
Just a minute, Listen to me, pIease!
This eIection is about our chiIdren's future,
So ask yourseIf...
...what kind of future wiII it be if you eIect
a man who has never taught a student...
...or even been to a PTA meeting,
This is a man who beIieves the pIuraI
of "goose" is "sheep"!
I'm the right person for the job,
Vote for me,
Lois!
Wait, I'm not done,
Peter! Come on! Stop,
Shut up! You guys shut up!
l didn't enjoy humiliating Peter,
but what choice did l have?
That's okay, Lois. l enjoyed it.
As soon as the polls close,
we can put all this ugliness behind us.
Lois Griffin is a sIut,
What?
Hi, I'm Peter Griffin,
I grew up in this town,
Quahog needs a moraI,
upstanding schooI board president,
Someone we can trust,
A Iot of nasty things
have been said during this campaign,
But pictures are better than words...
...because some words are
big and hard to understand,
But here's something
everyone can understand!
Do you reaIIy want
your chiIdren's future in the hands of this?
I know I don't,
Paid for by the Peter Griffin
for SchooI Board President Committee,
Sorry, Lois,
"Lewd," "obscene," and "a little blurry"...
...just some of the words used to describe
Lois Griffin's prurient pic.
- Good morning. l'm Tom Tucker.
- And l'm Diane Simmons.
Yesterday, voters
overwhelmingly declared...
...that Lois Griffin is not the kind of person
they want running their schools.
Her husband, Peter Griffin,
was elected by a landslide.
What a great day! I just want to say...,
I am so freaking wasted!
SpIendid,
How deIightfuI to have mother back,
I heard that,
Damn!
Don't feel bad, Mom.
All my friends think you're hot!
They can't believe l came out of you!
Lois, l got a joke for you. How many losers
does it take to make me breakfast?
Just one! You!
l'm just kidding. French toast, please.
Don't even talk to me, Peter.
You humiliated your own wife!
And for what? To get that crazy
Mr. Fargas back in the classroom?
Who?
Peter, l cared about our schools.
All you cared about
was some stupid competition.
Winning was only half the battle.
lf you blow this chance to do something
good for our kids...
...you'll be the biggest loser!
Oh, yeah?
Peter Griffin is no loser!
When l'm through with our schools...
...our students'll be so smart
they'll be able to program their VCRs...
...without spilling piping hot gravy
all over myself.
This is Trisha Takanawa, here
with School Board President Peter Griffin.
Mr. President, you've accomplished
so much in just a few short weeks.
Thanks, Connie. l'm very excited about
our progress in revamping our schools.
For starters,
we're making sex education more fun.
"Vagina junction, what's your function?
"Taking in sperm and spitting out babies"
And our schools are the safest around...
...thanks to the hall monitor XL-K.
HaIt! Present haII pass!
Right here.
Second request, Present pass,
But.... Right here!
Security breach!
l guess Little Miss Free Spirit will think
twice before roaming the halls.
l've restocked our school library...
...with books of some
of our greatest movies and TV shows.
Because if we don't teach our kids to read,
how will they ever know what's on?
Mr. Griffin, this is impressive.
l've never seen kids
so enthusiastic about reading.
Thank you. That's what you voted for.
Hey, son, show the folks at home
what you got there.
Good Lord! That's a dirty magazine!
That's mine.... Shaft.
There might be a mineshaft
under this library.
All these kids are looking at pornography!
What kind of pervert
gave you kids this filth?
Chris Griffin. He got it from his dad.
There's quite a crowd outside.
l haven't witnessed pandemonium like this
since Ridiculous Day down at the deli...
...when prices were so low
they were ridiculous.
You said it, pally.
That's why l brought in the big guns.
Say "how do" to the Ragin' Cajun,
Mr. James Carville.
Oh, God. Oh, jeez!
Did somebody open
the Ark of the Covenant?
Now see, Peter, what you gotta do is
you gotta declare war! War!
Your only chance
of surviving this scandal...
...is to claim that Lois
gave your boy the pornography.
And he's right.
Pin it on the old ball and chain.
l can't do that.
Lois is mad enough at me without....
l'm sorry. l can't look at you!
l mean, l can handle ugly.
But this is like circus ugly.
Lois, l need your help. You gotta come
to my press conference this afternoon.
Lois, l could lose my presidency!
Too bad! l've already lost more than that!
Not my rainbow socks
with the individual toes?
No. l've lost my respect for you.
Because l need those socks.
We now take you live
to Peter Griffin Junior High...
...where embattled School Board President
Peter Griffin is fighting for his political life.
Throw the bum out!
Mom, what are you doing here?
l thought you were mad at Dad.
l am.
l just came to see him twist in the wind.
Are you and Dad gonna get a divorce?
Oh, honey. Maybe.
"A parent giving porno to their kid
is a terribIe thing...
"...but I'm here to teII you
that I'm innocent! "
Oh, yeah. Right.
"I didn't give those magazines to my son,
"My wife, Lois..., "
Lois!
Crap, Look, my wife, Lois, is the most
important person in the worId to me,
I gave my son those magazines,
Even worse, I turned a beautifuI gift from
Lois into something cheap and tawdry,
I just wanted to win so bad,
Now I know that some things
are more important than winning,
Lois, I onIy hope you can find it
in your heart to forgive me,
Oh, Peter!
So you're saying you're not only
a bad father, but a bad husband, too?
Have you the moral authority to lead?
Yes. No. And, screw it. l resign.
There's the President,
First Lady Lois,
Now boarding the heIicopter,
And so ends a dark and shameful chapter
in the history of Quahog, Rhode lsland.
One which leaves this reporter asking:
How much moral bankruptcy and
perversion must we, the people, endure?
Next up, stay tuned for our
special investigative report...
Nature's Rubik's Cube."
Welcome back, Fargas.
Thank you.
Welcome back, Farg.
Much obliged.
HaIt, Present haII pass,
Excuse me?
Second request,
Present haII pass,
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru